<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TextStream</string>
    <string name="os_obj">Objectives\n
1.Understand the fundamental concepts of operating systems, including process and thread management, scheduling mechanisms, and memory management strategies.\n
2.Explore emerging trends and advancements in operating systems.</string>
    <string name="cn_obj">Objectives\n
1.Understand network layering, TCP/IP protocols, and end-to-end data flow.\n
2.Learn about network components, addressing, and routing.</string>
    <string name="gt_obj">Objectives\n
1.To comprehend graphs as modeling and analysis tools.\n
2.To introduce various data structures with graph theory.\n
    3.To learn graph theoretic algorithms.\n
    4.To understand graph coloring and covering.\n
    5.To learn the usage and applications of graphs in social networking and media.</string>
    <string name="wt_obj">Objectives\n
1.To learn the basic object oriented concepts using Java language.\n
2.To understand the advanced features of Java language.\n
    3.To understand the essential client side technologies for web programming.\n
    4.To develop applications using database connectivity and server side programming in
Java environment.\n
    5.To develop smart device based web application and deploy in different platforms.</string>
    <string name="ce_obj">Objectives\n
1.To learn about automata theory and regular expressions.\n
2.To learn the concepts in the design of compilers.\n
    3.To learn about the runtime store organization.\n
    4.To know the data structures used to implement symbol tables.\n
    5.To be familiar with garbage collection.</string>
    <string name="adb_obj">Objectives\n
1.To learn the fundamentals of data modeling and design in advanced databases.
2.To study the working principles of distributed databases.
3.To have an introductory knowledge about the query processing in object-based
databases and its usage.
4.To understand the basics of spatial, temporal and mobile databases and their
applications.
5.To learn emerging databases such as XML, Data warehouse and NoSQL.</string>
    <string name="dld_obj">Objectives\n
1.To learn Boolean algebra and simplification of Boolean functions.
2.To learn to design and analyze different combinational circuits.
3.To study the basics of synchronous sequential logic, analyze and design sequential
circuits.
4.To learn about basic memory devices and programmable logic devices to build
simple digital systems.
5.To learn to write code in Hardware Definition Language for designing larger digital
systems.</string>
    <string name="os_book">Operating Systems.pdf</string>
    <string name="cn_book">Computer Networks.pdf</string>
    <string name="gt_book">Graph Theory.pdf</string>
    <string name="wt_book">Web Technologies.pdf</string>
    <string name="ce_book">Compiler Engineering.pdf</string>
    <string name="adb_book">Advances in Database.pdf</string>
    <string name="dld_book">dld.pdf</string>
</resources>